Hi, in this section we will build a currency converter up that takes an amount of money
with the source currency, target currency, and then shows the converted value using light exchange rates.
Let's talk about the functionality. The user will simply type a number, for example the 500, and imagine I'd like to
exchange doors to, for example, the pounds, the prison pounds, and I click just simply exchange rate, and the
up you've fetched away the rates from the internet, and this was a result in a clean and readable way.
So we also have a swap feature. I talk about this button, so when user'd like to quickly swap
the currencies between like converse the pounds into doors, the same amount, he can click on the swap
button, and click get exchange rate again, and it will be recalculated. Also let's talk about the
formatting. We will make the sure the amount is formatted nicely, for example if I'd like to convert
a bigger amount, so we use a thousand separator, and we have also the decimal separator,
so it's how the currency is formatted. We also prevent user from selecting same currencies.
For example if I'd like to choose the doors, the USD, you cannot choose it, it will be disabled,
makes it easier and more intuitive. We prevent them choosing the same currencies from both sides,
and for example from two currency, you cannot choose the pounds, it will be disabled.
We also load rates from API. All available currencies will be loaded directly from the API,
so the least is always up-to-date. We also display counterplugs. We will generate these
images automatically, making it easy to identify each currency visually, and then the app will feel
simple to use, fast, and polished. So let's wrap up. What they're building is real work in currency
converter with smart eX decisions, live data, lineari, and improvements guided by AI. A small but
complete app ready to show an extent fuzzer. This is what they're built with you in this section,
only using COSOR AI, so let's get started.